Guide to the National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition records, 1993-2006.
National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition records, 1993-2006.
6843
6 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, and logo templates designed by Bonnie Acker.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
National Sustainable Agricultural Coalition (NSAC), based in Washington, D. C., was created out of two successful grassroots organizations, the Sustainable Agriculture Coalition (SAC) and the National Campaign for Sustainable Agriculture (NCSA). The National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition (NSAC) is a national alliance of farm, rural development, and conservation groups that organized in 1988 to affect federal agriculture policy. NSAC's vision of agriculture is one where a safe, nutritious, ample, and affordable food supply is produced by a legion of family farmers who make a decent living pursuing their trade, while protecting the environment, and contributing to the strength and stability of their communities.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, and logo templates designed by Bonnie Acker.
SUBJECTS
Names:
National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition.; Acker, Bonnie, 1948-; National Campaign for Sustainable Agriculture.; National Sustainable Agriculture Coalition.; Sustainable Agriculture Coalition.
Subjects:
Conservation.; Sustainable agriculture.; Grassroots organizations.; Rural organizations.; Natural resources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Permission for use is required from the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Office of Admissions.
CONTAINER LIST
- Policy, Reports, Documents, Meetings, Retreats, Memos, 1994-2006 (Box 1)
- Press Clipping, 1994-2003 (Box 1)
- Family Farm Opportunity Program, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
- Logo Design Information - Bonne Acker (Box 1)
- Executive Committee Notes, 1996-2004 (Box 2)
- Research Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 2)
- National Commission on Small Farms, 1995-1998 (Box 2)
- Newsletter Chronological File, 1994-2006 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 2)
- Budget, Appropriations, 1995-2001 (Box 3)
- Organizational Information, 1996-2000 (Box 3)
- CD - National Coalition on Sustainable Agriculture (Box 4)
- CD - Pam Brownings Folders and Files (Box 4)
- CD - Audio Annual Meeting, 2004 (Box 4)
- Board Meeting Material, 2002-2006 (Box 4)
- Annual Meeting, 2002-2005 (Box 4)
- Farm Bill Policy, 1995-1997 (Box 4)
- Press - Articles, 1997-2002 (Box 4)
- National Organic Rule, 2000 (Box 4)
- Media Plan Information, 1994 (Box 5)
- Northeast Sustainable Agriculture Working Group (NESAWG), 1996-2000 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous Committee Meetings, Notes, Memos, 1996-2000 (Box 5)
- Farm Bill Policy Options, 1995-1997 (Box 5)
- Signed-On Organizations (Box 6)
- Newspaper Clips, 1995-2001 (Box 6)
- Organizing Packet, 1995 (Box 6)
- Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 6)